[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Teddy Bear was named in honor of President Theodore Roosevelt, who refused to shoot a bear while on a hunting trip in this state.", "correct_answer": "Mississippi", "incorrect_answers": ["Florida", "Alaska", "California"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the smallest frog?", "correct_answer": "Brazilian Gold Frog", "incorrect_answers": ["Red-Eyed Tree frog", "Cane Toad", "Monte Iberia Eleuth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the German word Schreck from which Shreks name is derived?", "correct_answer": "Terror", "incorrect_answers": ["Monster", "Green", "Vampire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This very unusual plant, seen quite frequently during the Yuletide season, is a parasite growing on the branches of trees and deriving its nourishment from them.", "correct_answer": "All of the these", "incorrect_answers": ["Birdlime", "Mistletoe", "Golden Bough"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which answer best describes how many Congressional Medal of Honor medals were awarded during the Civil War", "correct_answer": "Between 1200 and 2000", "incorrect_answers": ["Less than 600", "Between 2000 and 4000", "Between 600 and 1200"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1994 comedy Dumb and Dumber, how many times do Lloyd and Harry say yeah while singing to Mental in the car?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["8", "0", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does the clothing brand Lacoste offer ophthalmic glasses as well as sunglasses?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the diet of the koala almost exclusively consist of?", "correct_answer": "Eucalyptus leaves", "incorrect_answers": ["Grass", "All of these", "Insects"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is James Bonds favourite cigarette brand?", "correct_answer": "Morland Specials", "incorrect_answers": ["Pall Mall", "Gladstone", "Marlborough"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did Attack of the Giant Leeches hit the movie screens?", "correct_answer": "1959", "incorrect_answers": ["1955", "1953", "1952"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are rabbits associated with in Aztec mythology?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Drunkenness", "Parties", "Fertility"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Queen Elizabeth II of Great Britain is allowed by law to go practically anywhere she wants to in Great Britain.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]